<treatments>
	<treatment id='85'>
		<refs>
			<ref><![CDATA[<a target='_new' href='https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/19136437'>Gottstein B, Pozio E, Nöckler K. Epidemiology, diagnosis, treatment and control of trichinellosis. Clin Microbiol Rev 2009;22:127-45</a>]]></ref>
			<ref><![CDATA[<a target='_new' href='https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3311199'>Watt G, Silachamroon U. Areas of uncertainty in the management of human trichinellosis: a clinical perspective. Expert Rev Anti Infect Ther 2004;2:649-52. 14B</a>]]></ref>
		</refs>
		<![CDATA[
			<li> Albendazol: 200 mg cada 12 h po x 3 días, seguido de 400 mg cada 12 h por x 15 días
			<li> Mebendazol: 400 mg cada 8 horas por x 14 días
			<li> Prednisona 40 a 60 mg cada 24 horas x 3 a 5 días, seguido de una dosis decreciente		]]>
	</treatment>
	<treatment id='151'>
		<refs>
			<ref>M. Wéry, Int J Antimicrobial Agents, 4: 227-238, 1994</ref>
			<ref>J. Pépin in Advances in Parasitology vol 33, 1994</ref>
			<ref>M. Wéry, Int J Antimicrobial Agents, 4: 227-238, 1994</ref>
		</refs>
		<![CDATA[<li>Suramine (ITM): test avec 100 mg en perfusion. Le même jour 400 mg IV sur 4 h. 
			<li>Deuxième jour: 500 mg/ 4 hours. Puis 1 g IV par semaine, 6 semaines. (Cave! insuffisance rénale, dermatite exfoliative).
			<li>Traitement rapide: 1 g IV jour 1, 3, 6, 14, et 21.
			<li>En cas de symptoms cérébraux, associez, melarsoprol et prednisone.
		]]>
	</treatment>
	<treatment id='48'>
		<refs>
			<ref><![CDATA[<a target='_new' href='https://www.ijaaonline.com/article/0924-8579(94)90032-9/fulltext'>Lambertucci et al. Trans. Royal Soc. Trop. Med. Hyg. 83:354;1989</a>]]></ref>
			<ref><![CDATA[<a target='_new' href='https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3372337/'>Doherty et al. BMJ 313:1071-2;1996</a>]]></ref>
			<ref><![CDATA[<a target='_new' href='https://wikitropica.itg.be/display/wt/Trematodes+-+Blood+flukes+-+Schistosomiasis+-+Diagnosis+and+treatment+of+acute+%28symptomatic%29+schistosomiasis'>WikiTropica ITM Antwerp</a>]]></ref>
		</refs>
		<![CDATA[
			<li> Praziquantel, 2 x 20-30 mg / kg / day during 2-3 days.
			<li> Repeat after 3 to 6 months, one unique dose of 40 mg / kg.
			<li> Prednisone 20 mg / day during 3-5 days.		
		]]>
	</treatment>
	<treatment id='38'>
		<refs>
			<ref>Hogan J1, Radhakrishnan J. The treatment of minimal change disease in adults. J Am Soc Nephrol. 2013 Apr;24(5):702-11.</ref>
			<ref>Ulinski T1, Aoun B. New treatment strategies in idiopathic nephrotic syndrome. Minerva Pediatr. 2012 Apr;64(2):135-43.</ref>
		</refs>
		<![CDATA[
			<li>Prednisone 60 mg/jour, 15 jours. Dosage dégressif.
		]]>
	</treatment>
	<treatment id='13'>
		<refs>
			<ref>Adamolekun B1, Hiffler L1. A diagnosis and treatment gap for thiamine deficiency disorders in sub-Saharan Africa? Ann N Y Acad Sci. 2017 Oct 24. doi: 10.1111/nyas.13509.</ref>
		</refs>
		<![CDATA[
			<li>Thiamine 3x250 mg IV/j pendant 3 jours, suivi de 300 mg/j per os pendant 2 semaines.
		]]>
	</treatment>
</treatments>